ever since the war Party massacre, Our lands go on patrols on our borders unguarded.
We have no war chief to lead us.
Isn't that Russia's job
before you make the journey to mother's crown and beyond?
Is there any chance you could search for Sona?
Where was she last seen?
The War Party Massacre site.
A wooded hollow across from devil's thirst on this side of the river.
You might be able to pick up her trail there if she went after the killers who attacked the proving.
Who killed those?
Be love, who tried to kill you again.
I'll see what I can do
my whole life, all of it in the embrace.
The world just got bigger,
but also more dangerous
be you
nor village upon the heights.
They say she fought beside Boston.
You're a lawyer, aren't you?
They say you've been made a seeker with rite of passage from the sacred land.
Yes, To track the killers who attacked the proving.
I can't imagine leaving all mother's protection.
But my sister Nicola is like you
Fearless.
She went north to find a Kharja officer called design.
Did the Matrix really give Niko a permission to leave?
No, they refused her, but nothing could stop her from going after site.
For 10 years, Kharja attacked without warning.
Devils like Sayyed butchered braves and kidnap civilians from blood sacrifice.
It all ended when the mad Son King died.
The matriarch say his son wants to set things right.
But that wasn't enough for a nickel.
He murdered our father doing the red rates.
The co aside,
hidden in the cellar, forced herself to watch.
You changed it.
You could have gone with her.
Leave the sacred land and be purged from all mother's eternal memory.
No, I begged Nicola to stay so she could avoid that.
She said she didn't care.
I don't know.
Will she really be cursed for avenging our father?
It seems
cruel.
I'm really worried about her.
I'll keep an eye out for him.
Oh, Mother, bless you.
I know the matriarchs won't let her return to the sacred land.
I just need to know that she's all right.
She must have passed through mother's crown.
My aunt's ally lives there.
They might have spoken.
Maybe she can tell you more.
Mother, You
I kneel before you low and humble,
pleading for strength.
and understand.
Can you see beyond your sacred domain?
Is your eternal memory encompass the world
If it dies
and watch over.
I think
that brave
It sounds like he's suffering.
He was one of the war party wounded in battle down the ridge.
There
he was too weak to be carried back to mother's heart,
so they brought him here.
Could you see the ambush from here?
I heard it.
Explosions and screams and
house of machines like monsters.
That's what he keeps growing and muttering about machines like nightmares, ripping everyone to shreds.
I've seen people die before,
but never in such pain.
I wanna be strong like you.
I I take it you know who I am.
I do.
I know a lot of people didn't want you in the proving.
If you hadn't been there, everyone would have died.
Shows how much we know
the very person we needed with someone the tribe never wanted.
I wish I could borrow some of your courage now for him.
You don't need to borrow what you already have.
Nothing I do comforts him.
I don't even have any dream will go to ease his pain.
There should be someone Stashes along brave chills to the east.
But
I must keep vigil for this man.
I'll cheque the Stashes for Dream Willow.
If I get a chance, you will
Thank you.
My only wish is to ease this poor man's suffering.
No,
right.
This must be with a war party.
Got massacred.
Such destruction.
Maybe the war chief left something behind some clue as to where she went.
Lots of machines,
Well controlled by the killers.
They sent a stampede of them down the slope.
Nora managed to take down a character, but not before the killers used it to send the other machines against them.
Scraps of food.
The killer's rested here before springing the trap Lunch before a blood bath.
Monsters.
You there.
The dead and wounded all cleared away.
They're no more braves or healers here.
Just me.
You're hurt.
What happened?
What didn't.
It's madness out there were.
Chief Sona sent me back to report.
I'm no good to her.
Like this
viral told me that the war chief tracked the killers.
Did she find them?
We followed their trail, but again and again they sent corrupted machines to attack us.
My room's started to slow me down.
So the war chief sent me back to let others know she hasn't given up the fight.
So you were here when the war party was ambushed?
I wass I thought after the proving there could be no darker day.
But I was wrong.
The war chief was delayed gathering the rearguard.
Eager for revenge.
The Braves in the lead fell into the trap.
Dozens lost in minutes.
If Sona hadn't arrived in rally Dis, no one would have survived.
Viral sent me to look for Sona.
Do you know where she is now?
All I can tell you is where we parted near the metal tower, southeast of the ruins of devil's thirst.
Look to the rise behind it with a lone boulder.
All head for the embrace and report what I know to Pharrell in the others.
May all mother lend you strength.
You'll need it going alone.
My focus is picking up some kind of signal.
Maybe I can scan it.
That's it.
Where is that coming from?
Those rooms That must be devil's thirst.
The city of the old ones of the metal.
Yeah.
Grazer place storage canister rotor blades.
Destroying these components will disable rotor blade attacks.
Looks just like Ross described.
Must be coming from its head.
I need to get up there.
You
tall neck information antennas could be used.
His climbing holds radar information storage hub override to access local area information.
I think I can leap onto the tonic from here.
All right.
No, I just have to reach its head.
Just give me a moment and I'll be off.
You're
how
long?
Sense what?
It sees two other machines
observing us.
Dash dot Dash 17 14 23 in one second for F ade.
Initiate cycle 80823
Routing query sends 14 23 in two seconds.
No response time.
15, 24 11 seconds.
Ping inert agents 14 24 12 seconds.
43 slash 46 Doormen.
All I can tell you is where we part nearthe metal tower, southeast ruins of double spurs Look to the rise behind it with our own gold
people,
this must be the rise.
Sonus Runner told me about
dressing rooms.
They must have taken a moment to rest.
Ayrault shorts.
That old Bo.
I see a lot of action.
Recent kills fresh skin.
The war chief stopped here.
So where did she go next?
Couldn't have been easy going on after the ambush.
The runner wasn't the only one who got hurt.
It might be a blood trail.
I could follow.
I should try.
My focus
tracks
fruits and blood.
Looks like Sona and her braves headed for that.
Rich
did Sawtooth.
Maybe Sona took it out.
She could be close.
You're lucky.
I happened by one heartbeat, Mohr.
And that sort of would have tourney you apart.
Half a heartbeat more.
And I would have killed it myself.
Uh, So your war chief Sona Varro asked me to find you.
Has he held the gate?
He has bravely.
I saw him kill a corrupted machine himself.
But he worries for you.
Our tribe needs strength, not sentiment.
I've tracked some of the killers who struck the proving.
I crave vengeance.
Do you?
You have no idea.
Show me.
Then Lend me your strength.
Follow
killers There.
Just across this ridge, digging the cursed earth.
The sin of the ancients is buried in that soil.
Corrupted demons.
I know.
I killed when it matters much
clean.
I wonder if you live up to it.
Hours ago as an braves into hiding in the trees below.
On my signal, we'll attack the enemy and their demonic machines outnumber us.
But we will have fury on our side.
We could have more than that Explain.
That's ways what we used to burn.
They used to blast.
It's how they dug out this pitch.
So we put fire to it and then boom!
Then let us begin.
Wait!
Let's not rush.
Give me some time to make an approach If I end up alerting them Open fire!
All right,
let's see what you Khun!
D'oh!
No!
Whose body is that?
Farewell
four.
No!
Follow my lead.
You!
Yeah,
Finish this.
Picking my target now.
An easy shot.
No,
this wasn't all The killers accounted more of the war Party massacre.
If I have to chase their filthy shadows from here two spears rich will you're hurt losing blood.
My health is not concerned.
No one doubts your determination.
But you need rest.
She's right, war chief.
Give your wounds.
Time to close.
Vaal.
What are you doing here?
I ordered you to hold that gate with your life.
And so I did until the runner you sent returned with news of his encounter with a Loy and your location.
I left the gate well guarded.
My place is here with you.
With our vengeance, I might not hold that.
Um maybe I should have a look around, See if I can figure out where the rest of the killers are.
Do as you wish.
Everyone else does, Mother.
No!
Yeah,
Commanders Over the past month, accidental blaze explosions have killed a dozen man here in the ring of Metal.
I've taken the precaution of placing our entire stockpile in a covered shelter safe from stray sparks and lightning.
And I've posted guards to control access.
I urge you to take similar measures or suffer the consequences.
Supply Master thrown out
a boy stockpile inside their base.
Sabotage that and we win.
I found something.
The rest of the killers are camped inside a ring of metal.
Any idea what that means?
Damn them.
The ring of metal lies in the ruins of devil's grief.
That ground is taboo.
I will return to the matriarchs.
Beg them to make an exception.
There's no time for that.
Blood spilled calls for blood spilled.
If the ground is cursed and let our vengeance.
Sanctify it.
You bless.
Feel.
Please.
War Chief.
Break the taboo.
Definitely.
It is a cursed place.
But be a lawyer.
Secret blessing can protect us.
I'll send scouts ahead.
Our force will assemble at the cliff above Ran echoes and launch our attack from there.
Sounds like a plan.
See you there.
Thank you.
He might take that back when you see what I'm getting us into onto Devils grief.
Now,
now.
Full already
handy
sending these from trail
fire.
Bellow back.
Weakness to freeze.
Lay storage canister.
Cargo sack.
Destroying this component disables arranged elemental attack and triggers an explosion.
Gallant, Destroying this component will disable fire attacks and trigger an explosion Setting fire to anything in the area.
I can't get out of this
already.
No
couple.
This will help
there.
All right,
part
no.